T-minus 60 seconds!
It all comes down to this!
(Leonard:)I've got butterflies.
(Sheldon:)Don't get soft on me, Hofstadter.
(Sheldon:)I will slap those glasses
right off your face.
(Penny:)What's going on?
(Leonard:)Hey. We're about
to buy tickets for Comic-Con.
T-minus 45 seconds!
(Leonard:)They sell out incredibly fast,
but as long as one of us gets in....
(Sheldon:)Good Lord, this is not the time
for flirting! Keep it in your pants!
It's a whole lot
of weird before coffee.
T-minus 30 seconds!
(Raj:)Oh, I have to go
to the bathroom so bad.
Every year!
I told you, wear a diaper!
And I told you I get diaper rash!
15 seconds!
Oh, this is it!
(Leonard:)This is it.
(Howard:)Five, four, three,
(Howard:)two, one.
It's live. Go! Go! Go!
(Raj:)Anyone in?
-No!
-Not yet!
Do not stop refreshing your screens!
(Sheldon:)-Refresh.
-Refresh.
(All(repeatedly):)Refresh. Refresh....
(Penny:)Yeah, this is not
gonna be enough coffee.